# **Matthias Wens**

Staf van elzenlaan 30, 2550 Kontich, Belgium +32497 28 23 22 | matthias\_wens@hotmail.com

# **PROFILE**

Name: Matthias Wens

Address: Staf van elzenlaan 30, 2550 Kontich, Belgium

• Phone: +32 497 28 23 22

• E-mail: matthias\_wens@hotmail.com

• Date of birth: 22-08-1995

Place of birth: Wilrijk, Belgium

• Nationality: Belgian

• Gender: Male

• Marital Status: Single

#### **PROFILE**

I am an engaged student in Master of Electronics and ICT Engineering Technology at KULeuven. I have an advanced skillset in Python programming and have leadership experiences. I am currently searching for a job in python or java developing.

Masterthesis – Developing of a multi-monitor webclient for medical image respresention

# **EDUCATION**

#### KULeuven, Campus De Nayer Sint-katelijne-waver, Belgium Master of Electronics and ICT Engineering Technology (not yet finished) 2017-2018 KULeuven, Campus De Nayer Sint-katelijne-waver, Belgium Bachelor of Electronics and ICT Engineering Technology (Magna cum laude) 2014-2017 **KULeuven** Heverlee, Belgium Bachelor of ICT Engineering (not finished) 2013-2014 Sint-ritacollege Kontich, Belgium Grieks-wiskunde 2007-2013

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### OTHER EXPERIENCE

E-kring

Sint-katelijne-waver, Belgium

Praeses

2017-2018

- Communication with professors and assistants.
- Leading meeting of the center-group of the organization (Praesidium).
- Attending meetings with other praesesses.
- Responsible for the organization, built-up, clean-up, ... of all activities.

E-kring

Sint-katelijne-waver, Belgium

Cursusdienst

2016-2017

- Communication with professors and assistants.
- Making sure that fellow-students receive printed course documents after they ordered and paid for them.
- Participating in the meetings of the center-group of the organization (Praesidium).
- Helping with built-up, clean-up, ... of activities.

Schoolrock Festival

Kontich, Belgium

Coördinator

2012-2013

- Leading function in the organisation of Schoolrock Festival, a festival organised by approximately 90 students of Sint-ritacollege, Kontich, Belgium
- Follow up the different working groups of students.
- Leading the meetings of the center-group of the organization.
- Participate in meetings with police, fire department, municipality, mayor, school principal, ...
- Coordinate the different events during the building of the festival, the festival itself and the clean-up afterwards.

**Schoolrock Festival** 

Kontich, Belgium

Co-operator Terrain unit / Chief of Main Entrance

2011-2012

- Participating in meeting of the working group "Terrein".
- Placing orders for stages, Pa installations, ...
- Responsible for the Entrance, Personal search and Ticketing control during the Festival. Leading function over approximately 20 students.
- Participate in built-up and clean-up of the festival.

# **SKILLS**

- Dutch (Mother language)
- Good understanding of both written and spoken English
- Conversational in French
- Holding a full car driver's license.
- Advanced level skills in Microsoft Office Suite/Libre Office.
- Programming:

Advanced: Python2/3, Java (JavaEE), JavaScript

Good: C, C++, C# (.NET), PHP, XML

# **HONOR & AWARD**

# Winner of Google Hashcode in the Antwerp Hub

Antwerp, Belgium

Google (Hosted by Taglayer)

2017

Winner of the online qualification round of Google Hashcode in the Antwerp Hub.

#### **OTHER**

Kazou vzw Antwerp, Belgium

Animator 2011-now

Accompany and animate children aged 15-16 on a vacation.

Creactief vzw Mortsel, Belgium

Swimming Instructor 2011-now

Teaching children (Ages 4-14) to swim

**Judoclub Kim-budo** Kontich, Belgium

Judo assistant Trainer 2010-now

Helping the trainer with the judo trainings.

Training the youngest group of judoka's.

# **HOBBY**

- Rock climber
- Pianist and guitarist